{
    "id": "7b8cf3a5fbbf4e64931ca89627a59059",
    "title": "Prepositions at, on, in, to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d852faed37b34e8c84f9e112835f348d",
            "title": "Prepositions At, On, In, To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Let’s go ……………… Smith’s for tea.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why are you staring ……………. her like that?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He works …………….. a factory.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went ……………… Canada last year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to see my brother ………….. Canada.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you shout ……………… Mary and tell her that breakfast is ready?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "to",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Turn right ……………….. the next corner.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a student ……………. Oxford.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There aren’t many mangoes ……………. the tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Agra is ………………. river Yamuna.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}